bootscootintraffic.com 2019-03-19

# BootScootinTraffic is Back!

Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the BootScootinTraffic.com and Sunny Suggs and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Sunny Suggs include BootScootinTraffic.com and Sunny Suggs. The Sunny Suggs website is a membership site. By using the Sunny Suggs website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information  
Sunny Suggs may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Sunny Suggs. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Sunny Suggs website.

Sunny Suggs encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Sunny Suggs so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Sunny Suggs is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Sunny Suggs website.

Use of your Personal Information  
Sunny Suggs collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Sunny Suggs may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Sunny Suggs and its affiliates. Sunny Suggs may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Sunny Suggs does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Sunny Suggs may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. Sunny Suggs may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Sunny Suggs, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Sunny Suggs may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Sunny Suggs, in order to determine what Sunny Suggs services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver

customized content and advertising within Sunny Suggs to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Sunny Suggs will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Sunny Suggs or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Sunny Suggs; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Sunny Suggs, or the public.

Security of your Personal Information

Sunny Suggs secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

Children Under Thirteen  
Sunny Suggs does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

Opt-Out & Unsubscribe  
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Sunny Suggs by contacting us here:  
\- Web page:   
\- Email:   
\- Phone: 

Changes to this Statement  
Sunny Suggs will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Sunny Suggs encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Sunny Suggs is protecting your information.

Contact Information  
Sunny Suggs welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Sunny Suggs has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Sunny Suggs at:

Sunny Suggs  
405 Arthur Dr  
Hurst, Texas 76053

Email Address:  
support@BootScootinTraffic.com

Telephone number:  
214.497.6982

Effective as of April 14, 2016
